(Penny:)Sheldon?
(Leonard:)Hello.
(Penny:)What are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)I have troubles, Penny.
(Sheldon:)I've come to pour them out
(Sheldon:)to the sympathetic ear
of the local barkeep.
(Penny:)You know, they have
a really nice bar
(Penny:)over at the Olive Garden.
(Sheldon:)I don't like the Olive Garden.
(Sheldon:)They treat me like family.
(Penny:)Okay, Sheldon.
What can I get you?
(Sheldon:)Alcohol.
(Penny:)Could you be
a little more specific?
(Sheldon:)Ethyl alcohol.
(Penny(pouring out a shot of tequila):)40 milliliters.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, honey.
I don't know milliliters.
(Sheldon:)Ah. Blame President James
"Jimmy" Carter.
(Sheldon:)He started America on a path
to the metric system
(Sheldon:)but then just gave up.
(Sheldon:)He wonders why he
was a one-term president.
(Penny(pouring out a shot of tequila):)Would you say that's
about 40 milliliters?
(Sheldon:)More or less.
Great.
(Penny:)Now, where were we?
(Sheldon:)I believe you were about
to ask me to choose a cocktail.
(Sheldon:)Fortunately, thanks
to computer-savvy alcoholics,